

George Vorobyov

Lead + senior product designer, UX/UI

www.geovo.me hello.geovo@gmail.com @meisdigital I'm a designer who cares about making beautiful things that help people. With 10 years of experience across brand and data-driven product design, I do help industry leaders and startups to reach new heights.

Career

User research Design thinking
Leadership Figma iOS 16
Material 3 Midjourney/ChatGPT
Design systems UX patterns
Adaptive design Autolayouts
Variants Animated prototypes
HTML/CSS CJM GA/Amplitude
Information architechture JIRA
JIRA Notion/Confulence
A/B testing Edge scenarios

Senior product designer

Quintegro Apr 2023 - Present Designed 4 key products for a popular US brand with a turnover of \$500 million.

Lead product designer

AdGuard

Feb 2020 - Mar 2023

Implemented new process to launch 5 company's products for over 25M monthly active users.

Lead product designer

Medaboutme

Apr 2018 - Feb 2020

Assembled a product team and built a process to launch a digital health ecosystem of 9 apps for 8M monthly active users.

Senior Product Designer

4Real

Feb 2016 - Apr 2018

Designed a popular in CIS online gaming playground with over 2M monthly visitors.

Product Designer

Deep Knowledge Group Dec 2012 – Feb 2016 Designed 12+ digital products for portfolio startups of the venture fund in Fintech, Big data, Al and other disruptive industries.

Educational training

State Belarussian Agricultural Academy

2007 - 2012

Master of applied maths and cybernetics